[narrator] With the detonation
of Miniature Rose
activated by the stopping of his heart,
Netero perished,
and when he died,
the King died along with him.
[both wailing]
[opening theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[singer singing in English]
[flesh cracks]
[both gasp]
[sentimental music playing]
[gasps]
[Shaiapouf] He's breathing!
[Menthuthuyoupi]
We have to hurry! Damn it!
The King doesn't have long!
This is bad!
And there's not enough time
to get him back to Pitou!
[Shaiapouf] It's going to be fine.
I will save the King myself.
[gasps]
[sobbing]
Hear me! Listen closely, my cells!
Go! Permeate the King, and heal him!
[dramatic music playing]
[both] Sire!
[Shaiapouf] Sire!
Are you all right?
How do you feel?
I am not worthy of praise
such as this, my King!
This is far too good.
And now that I have
experienced this taste,
I'll never, ever be able
to eat anything else but that in my life.
[Shaiapouf] Oh! Sire!
Sire! Oh, sire!
Please, please, no more!
Oh, please, sire,
I sincerely hope
you'll be willing to accept this as well.
[Shaiapouf gasps]
[panting]
[orchestra music playing]
[grunts]
[dripping]
[Meruem straining]
[Meruem] What rich and powerful depth
of flavor.
This could only have come
from the heavens above,
these veritable dewdrops of the angels.
[groans]
[orchestra music playing]
Sire!
[wails] Sire!
Oh, sire!
[gasping]
[Meruem] Try as I might,
I cannot compare the two.
I will declare without hesitation
both of them are supreme dishes.
[gasps]
[sighs]
[Meruem] I need more, more of both.
Give me all that you have…
and I will receive it,
so give me more of it.
[Menthuthuyoupi] Sire!
[Shaiapouf] Sire!
[Menthuthuyoupi] Yes!
[both] With pleasure!
[narrator] This was supreme bliss
and unparalleled joy.
[Shaiapouf] What is this?
[imperceptible]
[Menthuthuyoupi] What's this feeling?
From this point on, always,
you will refer to me as Meruem.
[both gasp]
[Meruem] For you see, that name…
is the name my mother gave me.
[chorus vocalizing]
[Shaiapouf gasping]
[chorus continues]
[narrator] By facing the King's
near-death and revival
and sharing the essence
of their own being,
Pouf and Youpi
underwent a transformation…
and became equals to the Queen,
the mother of their species.
[wind rushing]
[sinister music playing]
[suspense music playing]
[Menthuthuyoupi] It's clear
that his strength has increased.
[Menthuthuyoupi] The King's heartbeat,
his warmth.
We're even able to share
in the King's thoughts.
Maybe we should go back
to the palace first, sire.
If you still wish to feed,
there is more than enough to satisfy you.
[Meruem] "Feed"?
Oh, I see.
[dramatic music playing]
That taste was real after all.
[both gasp]
[Meruem] Even as I wandered
through the waning light,
I heard someone call my name.
"Meruem," they said.
-[wind blowing]
-[both gasp]
And now,
I cannot remember why I'm here.
Lord Meruem.
In fact, I am absolutely
overflowing with raw energy.
My mind, however, is clouded in fog.
[gasps]
Tell me, why do you look like that?
[shudders]
and will dispose…
-[gasps]
-[Menthuthuyoupi gasps]
Do you understand?
It makes no difference to me
if you do it out of affection.
Lying to me is a breach of trust.
So I did eat you.
I ate both of you.
We offered ourselves to you freely!
We know we stepped
way out of line, sire,
but it's what we really wanted.
[Meruem] Well, what happened?
Explain yourselves.
Before we do,
I'm afraid that I must
ask you a question.
It appears that you are able to recall
Perhaps, I should say instead
that I remembered them,
My Lord Meruem…
I think that you may be suffering
However, the human,
a coward and a scoundrel,
resorted to a devious,
underhanded trick
and utilized a powerful bomb,
betraying your good faith.
[Meruem] A duel. Yes, that's right.
I remember it now.
to kill you, sire.
However, none of us could bear
No, they belong entirely to you.
We merely returned
what was already yours
That will be the fastest way
for you to regain your memory.
[Shaiapouf] Well, well.
This… This is a golden opportunity!
If I return to the palace first…
He'll never even remember
who she was.
This will require convincing Pitou
and getting rid of that meddling human.
No, I know what I must do.
Before all else, I must end its life.
If he's running at full speed,
the King will still need 20 minutes
to reach the palace.
Oh, that's more than enough time
to kill her.
[gasps]
I can already fly.
-[Shaiapouf gasps]
-[Menthuthuyoupi laughs]
[Meruem] Which way to the palace?
North, sire.
You should be able to make it there
in about 15 minutes or so if you hurry up.
[wind blowing]
It's there.
[suspense music playing]
[Shaiapouf] He's fast.
I can't slow down, or he'll catch up!
Quickly! Quickly, my segments!
This is a gamble.
It won't be long before the King sees
the millions of humans
gathered outside the palace.
Then he'll remember everything.
[Knuckle] Hakoware!
[Palm] I've seen you
with my eye before…
before I was turned into a cocoon.
That means I'll always be able to see you,
no matter where you go.
WINK BLUE:
LONESOME DEEP SEA FISH
[Shaiapouf] What was that?
It felt like something
just attacked my segment.
Whatever it was, it came from nowhere.
I don't know.
It seems to have resulted
from the remaining enemies
It's the King.
The King is alive!
[closing theme music playing]
[singer singing in Japanese]
[upbeat music playing]
[Gon] Next time,
"Formidable Enemy and Clear Objective."
Know how people say, "like," a lot?
-[Killua] Sure.
-[Gon] So, like, do I say,
"Formidable, like,
Enemy and Clear, like--"
[Killua] Well, uh…
[singer singing in Japanese]